bestfreetemplates.org 2010-12-29

# Free Templates, Free Website Templates, Web Templates Directory

### **Privacy Policy**

**General** Website Templates Review ("BestFreeTemplates.org") tends to ensure the confidentiality and security of Your rights in every possible way.   
BestFreeTemplates.org ("BFT") also reviews this issue every now and then in order to ensure and protect the interests of our users in the most effective way and to make working with our website as fruitful and secure as possible.  
We strongly recommend You to review this part of our Privacy Policy to be well informed of the latest amendments and changes. 

**The information we collect** BFT collects information about its users in two steps: 

**Registration** To be able to submit his websites to BFT, our user has to register by filling out the registration form and provide the following information:  
\- Username  
\- Email Address  
We use the email provided by user only to inform him:  
-that his registration has been received   
-that his website submission was successful/unsuccessful  
-that his registration has expired  
We never use our users' emails in any other way, don't disclose them neither publically, nor to any third party. \- Password. 

**Website sibmission** Having completed Your registration, You are able to submit Your website(s) to BFT.  
For Your convenience we broke the process of collecting information into 5 steps (the 6 "payment" step is only for paid registrations):  
**1.** Indicate the type of Your Templates  
**2.** Provide information about Your website and the templates it offers:  
\- Site Name  
\- Site URL  
\- Description - You must provide absolutely unique description of Your website. Do not include to Your description the text (or part of the text) taken from Your site content. Also don't use the descriptions You used before, while registering Your website in web directories or catalogues.  
\- Advantages - Doesn't have to be Your site description. Must briefly describe advantages of the templates offered by the site You register. Please name only the distinctive features and advantages of Your templates.  
\- Number of templates  
\- Number of categories  
\- Template's average price  
\- Mark available types of products - Indicate the types of templates available on Your site.   
\- Support - Your technical support service (if any)  
\- Affiliate program  
\- Comission - If Your site has some affiliate programms, indicate the % of commission.  
\- Customization link - If You offer template customization services, include the link to this section of Your website.  
\- Telephone  
\- Fax - Your fax and telephone number will be shown on Your site profile page.  
\- Logo  
**3.** Link to each category page.  
Give links to Your site sections that correspond to each template category that You listed above.  
**4.** Upload previews of the last 4 templates.  
\- Upload the previews   
\- Indicate the links, template's positions and Regular price for each of the 4 previews.  
**5.** Provide examples of the websites developed on the basis of Your templates and affiliate sites. 

**Payment** We accept payments for submission to BFT made by credit card via PayPal system. The payment is maintained with strict confidentiality that doesn't allow to sell or use the received information for any other purposes. This is PayPay company that guarantees security of the payment process. BFT doesn't have access to the information You provide while making payment. That's why BFT is not responsible for safety of Your credit card information, as well as for any other personal data that You provide in the payment process. 

**Editing Your information** We allow the users who have websites registered in BFT to edit the information about their websites.   
You may change any information about Your website except the site URL and the personal information that You indicated in pre-registration. This option is available for everyone who is registered in BFT. 

**Links** BFT has many links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content of these websites. Always read the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use of these websites when You pass to them via BFT. 

**Website Security** We take all appropriate measures to ensure safety and security of the information about our users, as well as the security of our website.   
All billing information (such as Your credit card number and other) is being processed by PayPal - one of the best and most secure billing systems in the Internet. 

**Rates and Comments** BFT aims to provide its visitors with the most accurate and unbiassed information about the sites that offer web-templates in the Internet. We are interested in providing our users only with the best information. Our site has a special rating system that displays websites that offer the most qualitative and original webtemplates. Every visitor may leave his feedback to each of the registered websites. Our moderator periodically reviews all feedbacks in order to reveal unequal, abusive or spam comments. You may also inform us of the comments of this kind via "Contact" page.
